EXPERIENCES

Luca laconelli

Freelance-Contractor | July 2019 - now

Writer of performing and responsive applications for web, mobile and native; layout, style, best practices, accessibility, performance optimization, caching techniques, testing, debugging and offline access

Illimity Bank

Full stack developer | July 2019 - now

Writer of performing and responsive applications for web, mobile and native; layout, style, best practices, accessibility, performance optimization, caching techniques, testing, debugging and offline access

IT Auction

Full stack developer | April 2017 - July 2019

Studio Mado

Full stack developer | December 2015 - April 2017

IDEARTE Design

Co-Founder && Front end developer | December 2015 - July 2019

I've started a Digital Agency and i've worked on the planning and management about the setup of the entire company

SED Web Agency

Full stack developer | December 2014 - December 2015

Design and development of many e-commerce, e-learning platforms, landing pages and custom plugins on the WordPress platform plus the development of mobile applications

Beta Formazione

Front end developer | December 2013 - December 2014

Design and development of many e-commerce and e-learning platforms

Your3Minutes

Full stack developer | March 2014 - August 2014

Design and development of an online video-recruiting platform

Studio Abacus

Support teacher of computer science | May 2011 - August 2014

Teacher helping students learn how to be a developer

GEMOS Soc. Coop.

Problem solver and help-desk | July 2009 - December 2013

I've started my career by solving problem for people in a business with more than 1000 employees, doing code or whatelse

EDUCATION

Google online-Degree sponsored by a Google-scholarship

Google Mobile and Web Specialist | October 2017 - September 2018

Higher institute of IT, Math and Statistics

I.T.I.S. - Information Technology Abacus | September 2005 - July 2009

Philosophy, Math, German, Photography, Microsoft Office, Computer security

Extra-courses |

SKILLS

[{ "name": " Problem solving" }, { "name": " Full stack" }, { "name": " Creative" }]

- jQuery
- CSS
- WordPress
- ReactJs
- NoSQL
- VueJs
- MySQL
- NuxtJs
- W3C
- HTML
- AWS
- Performance
- Ionic

- NodeJs
- Git
- Accessibility
- Unit test
- E2E
- Jest
- Docker
- Cordova
- Webpack
- Vite
- PHP
- LaravelJavascript

- Agile
- Angular
- AngularJs
- Nativescript
- RestAPI
- Symfony
- Electron
- C#
- C++
- Java
- Lerna
- UI / UX
- Vitest

About me

With 15+ years in frontend development, I specialize in building high-performance applications using Vue.js and Nuxt.js. As an official Nuxt.js contributor and Vue conference speaker, I combine technical expertise with a passion for open-source and mentoring. Available for remote contract work worldwide. I am Graduated and Certified by Google.